It's one of those Simpsons jokes that we luckily didn't understand when we were kids.
On May 16, 1999, 30 Minutes was launched over Tokyo,
that in addition to showing us without futuristic culture, androids like sionants
and what Japanese companies are working on,
He told us this joke that no one understood.
Hello, I know a man from Nantóket.
AND?
Well, I think the stories about this are greatly exaggerated.
To understand it, we need to know the following.
A Libereak is a well-known style of power in English-speaking countries,
which consists of five rhyming verses according to the AABBA structure.
In the early 1900s this style became very popular,
as people come to support the use of this structure.
Among these nursery rhymes, the one that is perhaps the most famous says this.
Once upon a time there was a man from Nantóket,
whose virile member was so long that he could breastfeed him.
He said with a smile, wiping his chin.
If my ear were a female reproductive organ, I would make love to it.
So what I mean is listen to the protagonist of this nursery rhyme
and he thinks that his anatomical weakness has been somewhat exaggerated.